Leave gracefully.
[KARA] Or I’ll expose
your company for bribery.
You know,
in this digital age?
[PAUL] We wouldn't want
people to find out that…
you were the face
of your ex's company.
What does that make you?
A hypocrite?
Release it.
Make sure it’s during peak hours.
[ARIEL SPEAKS SIARGAONON]
Oh, my god!
“Hypocrite. She only used
the island for her own interests.”
People need to hear
your side of the story.
[KARA] Everything said about
me in the viral video is true.
But I'm here now,
not to clear my name,
but to fight to protect
the environment.
You didn't inform me you
were going to do a livestream.
I can handle myself, Jao.
You might as well just
say you don't need me.
[KARA]
I need you.
But not for the
reasons you think.
Sir, I think we have to
consider looking into alternatives
on how we can
develop the area.
So I'm proposing...
that we should build a
sustainable eco-resort.
Kara, Headquarters is
asking for your contact info.
They want to offer you the
international field officer position.
You're going
international, Kara!
But if I accept it,
do I have to leave the island?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Thanks.
So, Architect Zulueta
is setting up a meeting
with Team Pure Coast
to discuss the
integration of the mangrove
plantation into the eco-resort plan.
Sure.
Anytime.
Thank you, Jao,
for staying true to your word.
You really were on my side.
Actually, congratulations to us.
Our CEO saw...
your viral confession video.
[KARA]
Hm?
And that was actually
one of the deciding factors
on why he said yes to
build a sustainable, mangrove-friendly
eco-resort in Cabitoonan.
You know, Jao…
I was willing to expose the
irregularities of your company
even knowing you'd
get caught up in it.
Turns out…
your boss is really good
at covering his tracks.
[JAO CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You could've just asked
me yourself, you know?
I know where all
the bodies are, and...
I have receipts.
[KARA SCOFFS]
I really don't know why
you're taking this so lightly.
I almost chose the
mangroves over you.
Do you get that?
[JAO CHUCKLES]
Because, Kara,
I understand you.
I knew the moment
you learned that...
Young Horizon was
handling the project
and I was going to
be the project head,
I knew you'd want
me to resign
and join you in
taking down my boss.
But I realized I
couldn't do that
because I know
how he works.
And I'd have more leverage
if I stayed on his team.
And at the same time,
I could protect the
mangroves and you.
You know I can handle myself.
I know.
[JAO] But…
I’m here now.
You’re not alone anymore.
I'm just a little
disappointed because...
I was willing to sacrifice
us for the cause.
Let’s not…
Let’s not dwell on things
that haven't happened yet.
What matters is
we're in this together.
To protect the island
and the mangroves.
And most especially,
to protect each other.
[ALON BY JL]
[PEARL SCREAMS EXCITEDLY]
Oh, my god!
[PEARL GASPS]
- [PHONE RINGS]
- Pearl.
[PEARL ON THE PHONE]
OMG! OMG!
- [PEARL ON THE PHONE] OMG!
- [SIARGAONON] What is it?
- [SIARGAONON] Calm down!
- [PEARL ON THE PHONE] Ariel!
Ariel, I got accepted!
I got the scholarship!
[ARIEL SPEAKS SIARGAONON]
Wow! Really?
Oh!
[ARIEL SPEAKS SIARGAONON]
Is it true, Pearl?
[PEARL ON THE PHONE]
I thought this dream was a shot in the dark!
[SIARGAONON]
I'm so proud of you, Pearl!
I'm so, so proud of you.
[ARIEL SPEAKS SIARGAONON ON THE PHONE]
You're something else!
I'm just glad someone
believed in me.
Besides you, Mom, and Kara.
[ARIEL]
Of course, Pearl!
Wow!
Congratulations!
[SIARGAONON]
We’re going to celebrate!
Ariel...
[PEARL STUTTERS]
Wait, I just need to
do something, okay?
But thank you, Lord!
[PEARL GIGGLES]
Bye!
[PEARL BREATHES HEAVILY]
Hi, Sir Han!
I mean...
Song Ji Hoon.
You know what?
It actually doesn't matter who you are.
I just wanna thank you.
Thank you...
for believing in me.
Thank you for making me
feel that my dreams are valid.
Thank you...
for seeing my worth.
Because, Sir Han, I got accepted!
[PEARL LAUGHS]
All thanks to you!
You made me believe
that this island girl
can go out in the big world.
And I'm so happy!
[PEARL LAUGHS]
But I also hate you.
I hate that you're not answering
my calls or my messages.
I just want to make
sure if your family is okay.
If you're okay.
I hate that…
[PEARL CRIES]
that you're not here
to celebrate with me.
[PEARL SNIFFS]
And I hate you also
[PEARL CRIES]
for telling me
that you like me
then leave without even
asking me if I like you back.
‘Cause I do.
[PEARL CRIES]
You know…
scratch that.
[PEARL SNIFFS]
I lied.
I don’t just like you.
I love you, Sir Han.
I love you so much.
[PEARL SOBS]
[PEARL CRIES]
And it really hurts that you’re not
here because I miss you so much.
[PEARL SOBS]
[PEARL SNIFFS]
[PEARL BREATHES HEAVILY]
So?
Are you giving up?
What's on your mind?
Carol, do you think Jao
will ever really know me?
I don’t even know myself.
We’re obviously two
very different people.
We're just caught up in our emotions
and everything happening on the island.
[CAROL]
Kara...
you're both adults.
Caught up in your emotions?
What you mean is,
the honeymoon phase
with Jao is over.
And now you're
experiencing reality.
What exactly is the problem?
All this time,
I know I’m just hiding behind Kara.
But after everything
that’s happened, I realized
I want to figure out
who I am.
What do you mean?
Han shared a quote with me.
[CAROL]
Hm?
He learned it from a
Buddhist monk he once met.
It’s the philosophy of meta.
[CAROL]
Meta?
What does that mean?
It means...
wishing someone well
even though that person
will have a completely
different journey than yours.
Because love
is not possession.
It's freedom.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Kara.
These are the latest renders
Architect Zulueta sent for the project.
Um...
The mangroves are fully
integrated into the design already.
Noah's taken a look at it several times
and we've gone through several revisions.
You don't have
to show me this.
I know, but...
I want you to see
the whole process...
and how the project
is progressing.
I know you still have...
reservations about
the project, Kara, but…
I just want you to know
I'm grateful for your support.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Did you...
resign from the Cabitoonan
project because of me?
[KARA CLICKS TONGUE]
No!
[KARA LAUGHS]
I didn't resign, either.
I'm just focusing on
Del Carmen for now.
That’s good to know,
and, uh…
I promise you, all the...
environmental and
development programs
we promised Cabitoonan,
we will fulfill them.
And all the compliance,
everything that comes with it,
I'll personally make sure
we stay on top of it all, Kara.
I promise.
You don't have
to convince me.
[TANTAN]
Sir Handsome!
Hey, Tantan!
Ma'am Kara!
[JAO AND KARA LAUGH]
Okay,
I would like you to meet...
the first official hire
of Isla Gugma Resort.
Tantan.
Sir Handsome,
do I really have to wear a uniform?
I'm not used to it.
Oh, come on.
[KARA] It’s nice!
You look handsome!
[JAO]
Better get used to it.
[TANTAN]
Used to what?
The uniform or being handsome?
[KARA]
Yes.
Can I hit him?
[TANTAN AND KARA LAUGH]
[ARIEL] Why won't you
let us take you to Manila?
Because you'll just
cry there anyway.
Might as well stay here
and save your tears, right?
Hm.
I’m not crying.
[CAROL SNIFFS]
[CAROL]
Pearl...
stay strong, okay?
[SIARGAONON]
Be strong.
- Of course, Mom.
- [CAROL CRIES]
[SIARGAONON]
Take care, Princess Pearl.
[CRYING]
- Take a shot for me, Mom!
- Yes! Of course!
[CAROL AND PEARL LAUGH]
If you need anything,
just text or call, okay?
Jao, take care, okay?
I'm proud of you.
You got to do
what you wanted.
You did, too, Kara.
And whatever else
you set your mind to,
you will achieve it!
You’re Kara!
[KARA AND PEARL LAUGH]
[HAN BIN]
Pearl!
[PEARL]
Sir Han?
Sir Han!
Hey!
When did you get back?
I can't miss this
for the world.
Sir Han, why aren't you
answering your phone calls?
Pearl...
[KOREAN]
I love you.
Sir Han.
I got accepted into the
scholarship, Sir Han.
I know.
We can give a lot
of people jobs here.
[JAO]
Kara? Surprise visit?
Is Sir Paul really gone?
Officially fired last week.
Well, as long as I'm around,
no one can hurt you.
I'll let you know my
decision by Friday.
[CAROL] You know
I support you, right?
Wherever you decide to go.
- [KARA] Are you happy?
- [JAO] Yeah.
[JAO]
Because finally, I'm home.
And everything I need is here.
The island. You.
Jao, I'm leaving Siargao.
Please, Kara, don't.
Not now.